<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Sandra Fogg</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sandra Fogg, a second-year MESM student, graduated from the University of Rhode Island in 2015 with dual-baccalaureate degrees in Pharmaceutical Sciences and Biology. As an undergraduate research assistant, Sandra helped to discover novel antimicrobial compounds from unidentified marine bacteria and fungi. After graduating, her compounding interests in health and marine science yielded her a position at the Environmental Protection Agency, researching the toxicity of antihypertensive pharmaceuticals to mussels, oysters and clams. Her resulting collaboration with aquaculture farmers across the state ignited her interest in mariculture and fisheries. Sandra then traded in laboratory goggles for a SCUBA mask and headed to East Africa to study the diverse Cichlid fisheries in rural Malawi. Since her return, she been studying native California fishes, with research including a Coho salmon restoration project within the Russian River watershed and Chinook salmon spawning and juvenile outmigration in the Sacramento-San Joaquin Delta. Compelled by the relationship between humans and the sea, Sandra plans is specializing in Coastal Marine Resource Management at the Bren School. Her master&#39;s group project seek to identify the availability and suitability of marine aquaculture sites within Brazil&#39;s Exclusive Economic Zone. After Bren, she hopes to investigate how anthropogenic disturbances impact the health of harvestable marine species and food security for developing coastal regions around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
